<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="./resample.png" type="Manipulator" xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.10 http://knime.org/node/v2.10.xsd">
    <name>Resample/Warp (Reproject)</name>
    
    <shortDescription>
        Raster image resample, reprojection and warping node
    </shortDescription>
    
    <fullDescription>
        <intro>This node takes a list of raster file location in the input table, perform the warping using <a href="http://www.gdal.org/gdalwarp.html">gdalwarp </a>
        command and generate a list of output rasters in the desired location. The output table contains the generated raster file locations.  
        </intro>
        
        
        <option name="Resample method">Resampling method to use. the default value is "average"". Check <a href="http://www.gdal.org/gdalwarp.html">here</a> for details</option>
        <option name="Working memory">Set the amount of memory (in megabytes) that the warp API is allowed to use for caching. By default it is set to 500 MB</option>
        <option name="Source Spatial Reference Set">
        Source spatial reference set. The coordinate systems that can be passed are anything supported by the OGRSpatialReference.SetFromUserInput() call, which includes EPSG PCS and GCSes (i.e. EPSG:4296), PROJ.4 declarations (as above), or the name of a .prj file containing well known text.
        It is optional and can be empty.
        </option>
        <option name="Target Spatial Reference Set">
        Target spatial reference set. The coordinate systems that can be passed are anything supported by the OGRSpatialReference.SetFromUserInput() call, which includes EPSG PCS and GCSes (i.e. EPSG:4296), PROJ.4 declarations (as above), or the name of a .prj file containing well known text.
        It is optional and can be empty.
        </option>
        <option name="Output File Resolution (X and Y)">Set output file resolution (X and Y) (in target georeferenced units).  Both must be positive values.</option>
        <option name="Output format">Select the output format. The default is GeoTIFF (GTiff)</option>
        <option name="Target Aligned Pixels">Target aligned pixels. Check this box if you want to align the coordinates of the extent of the output file to the values of the output file resolution, such that the aligned extent includes the minimum extent.</option>
        <option name="Overwrite">Check this box if you want to overwrite the target dataset if it already exists.</option>
        <option name="Output Folder Location">Location of the output folder where your new raster files will be generated. 
        It will also generate a text file "commands.txt" in this location that contains all the commands use for generating raster.
        The commands in this file can be run separately as a batch file.</option>
        <option name="File Naming">There are two file naming convention here. If the first option "Use name of source file" is selected 
        then it will generate output the raster files with the same name of source raster file in the input table. This selection 
        will ignore the value in "Select input column" option. If the second option "Sub-directory based on column" is selected
        then it will generate output the raster files according to the values in selected column in ""Select input column"
        option. By default it is set to "Use name of source file".</option>
        <option name="Select input column">This works along with "File Naming" option</option>
        <option name="Run commands">Check this option if you actually want to run the gdal commands. You have option
         to run it from the generated "commands.txt" file as a batch script if you decide not to run it. By default it is checked.</option>
        <!-- possibly more options that can also be grouped by tabs -->
        <!--
        <tab name="Standard Options">
            <option name="short name of first option (like in the dialog)">description of first option</option>
            <option name="short name of second option (like in the dialog)">description of second option</option>
        </tab>
        <tab name="Advanced Options">
            <option name="short name of first advanced option (like in the dialog)">description of first advanced option</option>
        </tab>
        -->
    </fullDescription>
    
    <ports>
        <inPort index="0" name="Raster Location Table">The locations of source raster files. The table must contain a "Location" column.</inPort>
        <!-- possibly more input ports here-->
        <outPort index="0" name="Raster Location Table">The locations of generated raster file. It uses "Location" as column header.</outPort>
        <!-- possibly more output ports here-->
    </ports>    
    <views>
        <view index="0" name="No View">No view option available for this node</view>
        <!--view index="1" name="name of second view">Description of second view...</view-->
    </views>
</knimeNode>
